Menu

All the Policies below are for all the "\_\_\_\_.lioneur.com" (ex. podcast.lioneur.com, forms.lioneur.com,lead.lioneur.com and other) domains
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

* #### [Privacy Policy](javascript:void(0);)
    
* #### [Terms of Service & Community Member’s Confidentiality Pledge](javascript:void(0);)
    
* #### [Hosting and Maintenance](javascript:void(0);)

#### Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. It is Lioneur’s policy to respect your privacy and comply with any applicable law and regulation regarding any personal information we may collect about you, including across our website, [https://lioneur.com](https://wordtohtml.net/), and other sites we own and operate.

Personal information is any information about you which can be used to identify you. This includes information about you as a person (such as name, address, and date of birth), your devices, payment details, and even information about how you use a website or online service.

In the event our site contains links to third-party sites and services, please be aware that those sites and services have their own privacy policies. After following a link to any third-party content, you should read their posted privacy policy information about how they collect and use personal information. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any of your activities after you leave our site.

This policy is effective as of 13 June 2021.

Last updated: 13 June 2021

### Information We Collect

Information we collect falls into one of two categories: “voluntarily provided” information and “automatically collected” information.

“Voluntarily provided” information refers to any information you knowingly and actively provide us when using or participating in any of our services and promotions.

“Automatically collected” information refers to any information automatically sent by your devices in the course of accessing our products and services.

#### Log Data

When you visit our website, our servers may automatically log the standard data provided by your web browser. It may include your device’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser type and version, the pages you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on each page, and other details about your visit.

Additionally, if you encounter certain errors while using the site, we may automatically collect data about the error and the circumstances surrounding its occurrence. This data may include technical details about your device, what you were trying to do when the error happened, and other technical information relating to the problem. You may or may not receive notice of such errors, even in the moment they occur, that they have occurred, or what the nature of the error is.

Please be aware that while this information may not be personally identifying by itself, it may be possible to combine it with other data to personally identify individual persons.

#### Device Data

When you visit our website or interact with our services, we may automatically collect data about your device, such as:

* Device Type
* Operating System
* Unique device identifiers
* Device settings
* Geo-location data

Data we collect can depend on the individual settings of your device and software. We recommend checking the policies of your device manufacturer or software provider to learn what information they make available to us.

#### Personal Information

We may ask for personal information — for example, when you submit content to us or when you contact us — which may include one or more of the following:

* Name
* Email
* Social media profiles
* Date of birth
* Phone/mobile number
* Home/mailing address

##### Sensitive Information

“Sensitive information” or “special categories of data” is a subset of personal information that is given a higher level of protection. Examples of sensitive information include information relating to your racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion, trade union or other professional associations or memberships, philosophical beliefs, sexual orientation, sexual practices or sex life, criminal records, health information, or biometric information.

The types of sensitive information that we may collect about you include:

* Religion
* Philosophical beliefs
* Criminal records
* Health information
* Biometric information

We will not collect sensitive information about you without first obtaining your consent, and we will only use or disclose your sensitive information as permitted, required, or authorized by law.

#### User-Generated Content

We consider “user-generated content” to be materials (text, image and/or video content) voluntarily supplied to us by our users for the purpose of publication on our website or re-publishing on our social media channels. All user-generated content is associated with the account or email address used to submit the materials.

Please be aware that any content you submit for the purpose of publication will be public after posting (and subsequent review or vetting process). Once published, it may be accessible to third parties not covered under this privacy policy.

#### Legitimate Reasons for Processing Your Personal Information

We only collect and use your personal information when we have a legitimate reason for doing so. In which instance, we only collect personal information that is reasonably necessary to provide our services to you.

#### Collection and Use of Information

We may collect personal information from you when you do any of the following on our website:

* Register for an account
* Enter any of our competitions, contests, sweepstakes, and surveys
* Sign up to receive updates from us via email or social media channels
* Use a mobile device or web browser to access our content
* Contact us via email, social media, or on any similar technologies
* When you mention us on social media

We may collect, hold, use, and disclose information for the following purposes, and personal information will not be further processed in a manner that is incompatible with these purposes:

* to provide you with our platform’s core features and services
* to enable you to customize or personalize your experience of our website
* to deliver products and/or services to you
* to contact and communicate with you
* for analytics, market research, and business development, including to operate and improve our website, associated applications, and associated social media platforms
* for advertising and marketing, including to send you promotional information about our products and services and information about third parties that we consider may be of interest to you
* to enable you to access and use our website, associated applications, and associated social media platforms
* for internal record keeping and administrative purposes
* to run competitions, sweepstakes, and/or offer additional benefits to you
* to comply with our legal obligations and resolve any disputes that we may have
* to attribute any content (e.g. posts and comments) you submit that we publish on our website
* for security and fraud prevention, and to ensure that our sites and apps are safe, secure, and used in line with our terms of use
* for technical assessment, including to operate and improve our app, associated applications, and associated social media platforms

We may combine voluntarily provided and automatically collected personal information with general information or research data we receive from other trusted sources. For example, Our marketing and market research activities may uncover data and insights, which we may combine with information about how visitors use our site to improve our site and your experience on it.

#### Security of Your Personal Information

When we collect and process personal information, and while we retain this information, we will protect it within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use, or modification.

Although we will do our best to protect the personal information you provide to us, we advise that no method of electronic transmission or storage is 100% secure, and no one can guarantee absolute data security.

You are responsible for selecting any password and its overall security strength, ensuring the security of your own information within the bounds of our services. For example, ensuring any passwords associated with accessing your personal information and accounts are secure and confidential.

#### How Long We Keep Your Personal Information

We keep your personal information only for as long as we need to. This time period may depend on what we are using your information for, in accordance with this privacy policy. For example, if you have provided us with personal information as part of creating an account with us, we may retain this information for the duration your account exists on our system. If your personal information is no longer required for this purpose, we will delete it or make it anonymous by removing all details that identify you.

However, if necessary, we may retain your personal information for our compliance with a legal, accounting, or reporting obligation or for archiving purposes in the public interest, scientific, or historical research purposes or statistical purposes.

### Children’s Privacy

We do not aim any of our products or services directly at children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personal information about children under 13.

### Disclosure of Personal Information to Third Parties

We may disclose personal information to:

* a parent, subsidiary, or affiliate of our company
* third-party service providers for the purpose of enabling them to provide their services, including (without limitation) IT service providers, data storage, hosting and server providers, ad networks, analytics, error loggers, debt collectors, maintenance or problem-solving providers, marketing or advertising providers, professional advisors, and payment systems operators
* our employees, contractors, and/or related entities
* our existing or potential agents or business partners
* sponsors or promoters of any competition, sweepstakes, or promotion we run
* credit reporting agencies, courts, tribunals, and regulatory authorities, in the event you fail to pay for goods or services we have provided to you
* courts, tribunals, regulatory authorities, and law enforcement officers, as required by law, in connection with any actual or prospective legal proceedings, or in order to establish, exercise, or defend our legal rights
* third parties, including agents or sub-contractors, who assist us in providing information, products, services, or direct marketing to you
* third parties to collect and process data
* an entity that buys, or to which we transfer all or substantially all of our assets and business

Third parties we currently use include:

* Google Analytics
* sendinblue
* Google Adsense
* Facebook

### International Transfers of Personal Information

The personal information we collect is stored and/or processed in Ireland, and South Africa, or where we or our partners, affiliates, and third-party providers maintain facilities.

The countries to which we store, process, or transfer your personal information may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. If we transfer your personal information to third parties in other countries: (i) we will perform those transfers in accordance with the requirements of applicable law; and (ii) we will protect the transferred personal information in accordance with this privacy policy.

### Your Rights and Controlling Your Personal Information

**Your choice:** By providing personal information to us, you understand we will collect, hold, use, and disclose your personal information in accordance with this privacy policy. You do not have to provide personal information to us, however, if you do not, it may affect your use of our website or the products and/or services offered on or through it.

**Information from third parties:** If we receive personal information about you from a third party, we will protect it as set out in this privacy policy. If you are a third party providing personal information about somebody else, you represent and warrant that you have such person’s consent to provide the personal information to us.

**Marketing permission:** If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by contacting us using the details below.

**Access:** You may request details of the personal information that we hold about you.

**Correction:** If you believe that any information we hold about you is inaccurate, out of date, incomplete, irrelevant, or misleading, please contact us using the details provided in this privacy policy. We will take reasonable steps to correct any information found to be inaccurate, incomplete, misleading, or out of date.

**Non-discrimination:** We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your rights over your personal information. Unless your personal information is required to provide you with a particular service or offer (for example providing user support), we will not deny you goods or services and/or charge you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through granting discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties, or provide you with a different level or quality of goods or services.

**Downloading of Personal Information:** We provide a means for you to download the personal information you have shared through our site. Please contact us for more information.

**Notification of data breaches:** We will comply with laws applicable to us in respect of any data breach.

**Complaints:** If you believe that we have breached a relevant data protection law and wish to make a complaint, please contact us using the details below and provide us with full details of the alleged breach. We will promptly investigate your complaint and respond to you, in writing, setting out the outcome of our investigation and the steps we will take to deal with your complaint. You also have the right to contact a regulatory body or data protection authority in relation to your complaint.

**Unsubscribe:** To unsubscribe from our email database or opt-out of communications (including marketing communications), please contact us using the details provided in this privacy policy, or opt-out using the opt-out facilities provided in the communication. We may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity.

### Use of Cookies

We use “cookies” to collect information about you and your activity across our site. A cookie is a small piece of data that our website stores on your computer, and accesses each time you visit, so we can understand how you use our site. This helps us serve you content based on preferences you have specified.

Please refer to our Cookie Policy for more information.

### Business Transfers

If we or our assets are acquired, or in the unlikely event that we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, we would include data, including your personal information, among the assets transferred to any parties who acquire us. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any parties who acquire us may, to the extent permitted by applicable law, continue to use your personal information according to this policy, which they will be required to assume as it is the basis for any ownership or use rights we have over such information.

### Limits of Our Policy

Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and policies of those sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy practices.

### Changes to This Policy

At our discretion, we may change our privacy policy to reflect updates to our business processes, current acceptable practices, or legislative or regulatory changes. If we decide to change this privacy policy, we will post the changes here at the same link by which you are accessing this privacy policy.

If the changes are significant, or if required by applicable law, we will contact you (based on your selected preferences for communications from us) and all our registered users with the new details and links to the updated or changed policy.

If required by law, we will get your permission or give you the opportunity to opt in to or opt out of, as applicable, any new uses of your personal information.

### Additional Disclosures for Australian Privacy Act Compliance (AU)

#### International Transfers of Personal Information

Where the disclosure of your personal information is solely subject to Australian privacy laws, you acknowledge that some third parties may not be regulated by the Privacy Act and the Australian Privacy Principles in the Privacy Act. You acknowledge that if any such third party engages in any act or practice that contravenes the Australian Privacy Principles, it would not be accountable under the Privacy Act, and you will not be able to seek redress under the Privacy Act.

### Additional Disclosures for General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) Compliance (EU)

#### Data Controller / Data Processor

The GDPR distinguishes between organisations that process personal information for their own purposes (known as “data controllers”) and organizations that process personal information on behalf of other organizations (known as “data processors”). We, Lioneur, located at the address provided in our Contact Us section, are a Data Controller and/or Processor with respect to the personal information you provide to us.

#### Legal Bases for Processing Your Personal Information

We will only collect and use your personal information when we have a legal right to do so. In which case, we will collect and use your personal information lawfully, fairly, and in a transparent manner. If we seek your consent to process your personal information, and you are under 16 years of age, we will seek your parent or legal guardian’s consent to process your personal information for that specific purpose.

Our lawful bases depend on the services you use and how you use them. This means we only collect and use your information on the following grounds:

##### Consent From You

Where you give us consent to collect and use your personal information for a specific purpose. You may withdraw your consent at any time using the facilities we provide; however this will not affect any use of your information that has already taken place. You may consent to providing your name and contact details for the purpose of entering a giveaway or promotion. While you may withdraw your entry at any time, this will not affect any selection or judging that has already taken place. If you have any further enquiries about how to withdraw your consent, please feel free to enquire using the details provided in the Contact Us section of this privacy policy.

##### Performance of a Contract or Transaction

Where you have entered into a contract or transaction with us, or in order to take preparatory steps prior to our entering into a contract or transaction with you. For example, if you contact us with an enquiry, we may require personal information such as your name and contact details in order to respond.

##### Our Legitimate Interests

Where we assess it is necessary for our legitimate interests, such as for us to provide, operate, improve and communicate our services. We consider our legitimate interests to include research and development, understanding our audience, marketing and promoting our services, measures taken to operate our services efficiently, marketing analysis, and measures taken to protect our legal rights and interests.

##### Compliance with Law

In some cases, we may have a legal obligation to use or keep your personal information. Such cases may include (but are not limited to) court orders, criminal investigations, government requests, and regulatory obligations. If you have any further enquiries about how we retain personal information in order to comply with the law, please feel free to enquire using the details provided in the Contact Us section of this privacy policy.

#### International Transfers Outside of the European Economic Area (EEA)

We will ensure that any transfer of personal information from countries in the European Economic Area (EEA) to countries outside the EEA will be protected by appropriate safeguards, for example by using standard data protection clauses approved by the European Commission, or the use of binding corporate rules or other legally accepted means.

#### Your Rights and Controlling Your Personal Information

**Restrict:** You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information if (i) you are concerned about the accuracy of your personal information; (ii) you believe your personal information has been unlawfully processed; (iii) you need us to maintain the personal information solely for the purpose of a legal claim; or (iv) we are in the process of considering your objection in relation to processing on the basis of legitimate interests.

**Objecting to processing:** You have the right to object to processing of your personal information that is based on our legitimate interests or public interest. If this is done, we must provide compelling legitimate grounds for the processing which overrides your interests, rights, and freedoms, in order to proceed with the processing of your personal information.

**Data portability:** You may have the right to request a copy of the personal information we hold about you. Where possible, we will provide this information in CSV format or other easily readable machine format. You may also have the right to request that we transfer this personal information to a third party.

**Deletion:** You may have a right to request that we delete the personal information we hold about you at any time, and we will take reasonable steps to delete your personal information from our current records. If you ask us to delete your personal information, we will let you know how the deletion affects your use of our website or products and services. There may be exceptions to this right for specific legal reasons which, if applicable, we will set out for you in response to your request. If you terminate or delete your account, we will delete your personal information within 30 days of the deletion of your account. Please be aware that search engines and similar third parties may still retain copies of your personal information that has been made public at least once, like certain profile information and public comments, even after you have deleted the information from our services or deactivated your account.

### Additional Disclosures for California Compliance (US)

Under California Civil Code Section 1798.83, if you live in California and your business relationship with us is mainly for personal, family, or household purposes, you may ask us about the information we release to other organizations for their marketing purposes.

To make such a request, please contact us using the details provided in this privacy policy with “Request for California privacy information” in the subject line. You may make this type of request once every calendar year. We will email you a list of categories of personal information we revealed to other organisations for their marketing purposes in the last calendar year, along with their names and addresses. Not all personal information shared in this way is covered by Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code.

#### Do Not Track

Some browsers have a “Do Not Track” feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. At this time, we do not respond to browser “Do Not Track” signals.

We adhere to the standards outlined in this privacy policy, ensuring we collect and process personal information lawfully, fairly, transparently, and with legitimate, legal reasons for doing so.

#### Cookies and Pixels

At all times, you may decline cookies from our site if your browser permits. Most browsers allow you to activate settings on your browser to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. Accordingly, your ability to limit cookies is based only on your browser’s capabilities. Please refer to the Cookies section of this privacy policy for more information.

#### CCPA-permitted financial incentives

In accordance with your right to non-discrimination, we may offer you certain financial incentives permitted by the CCPA that can result in different prices, rates, or quality levels for the goods or services we provide.

Any CCPA-permitted financial incentive we offer will reasonably relate to the value of your personal information, and we will provide written terms that describe clearly the nature of such an offer. Participation in a financial incentive program requires your prior opt-in consent, which you may revoke at any time.

#### California Notice of Collection

In the past 12 months, we have collected the following categories of personal information enumerated in the California Consumer Privacy Act:

* Customer records, such as billing and shipping address, and credit or debit card data.
* Demographics, such as your age or gender. This category includes data that may qualify as protected classifications under other California or federal laws.
* Commercial information, such as products or services history and purchases.
* Internet activity, such as your interactions with our service.
* Audio or visual data, such as photos or videos you share with us or post on the service.
* Geolocation data.
* Employment and education data, such as data you provide when you apply for a job with us.
* Inferences, such as information about your interests, preferences and favorites.

For more information on information we collect, including the sources we receive information from, review the “Information We Collect” section. We collect and use these categories of personal information for the business purposes described in the “Collection and Use of Information” section, including to provide and manage our Service.

#### Right to Know and Delete

If you are a California resident, you have rights to delete your personal information we collected and know certain information about our data practices in the preceding 12 months. In particular, you have the right to request the following from us:

* The categories of personal information we have collected about you;
* The categories of sources from which the personal information was collected;
* The categories of personal information about you we disclosed for a business purpose or sold;
* The categories of third parties to whom the personal information was disclosed for a business purpose or sold;
* The business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling the personal information; and
* The specific pieces of personal information we have collected about you.

To exercise any of these rights, please contact us using the details provided in this privacy policy.

#### Shine the Light

If you are a California resident, in addition to the rights discussed above, you have the right to request information from us regarding the manner in which we share certain personal information as defined by California’s “Shine the Light” with third parties and affiliates for their own direct marketing purposes.

To receive this information, send us a request using the contact details provided in this privacy policy. Requests must include “California Privacy Rights Request” in the first line of the description and include your name, street address, city, state, and ZIP code.

### Contact Us

For any questions or concerns regarding your privacy, you may contact us using the following details:

Lioneur Webmaster  
[\[email protected\]](https://lioneur.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

We have appointed an internal Data Protection Officer for you to contact if you have any questions or concerns regarding your privacy, or our policies or practices. The Data Protection Officer’s contact details are as follows:

Lioneur Webmaster  
[\[email protected\]](https://lioneur.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

#### Terms of Service & Community Member’s Confidentiality Pledge

**Community Member’s Confidentiality Pledge**
---------------------------------------------

These Terms of Service govern your use of the website located at [https://lioneur.com](https://wordtohtml.net/) and any related services provided by Lioneur.

By accessing [https://lioneur.com](https://wordtohtml.net/), you agree to abide by these Terms of Service and to comply with all applicable laws and regulations. If you do not agree with these Terms of Service, you are prohibited from using or accessing this website or using any other services provided by Lioneur.

We, Lioneur, reserve the right to review and amend any of these Terms of Service at our sole discretion. Upon doing so, we will update this page. Any changes to these Terms of Service will take effect immediately from the date of publication.

These Terms of Service were last updated on 13 June 2021.

### Limitations of Use

By using this website, you warrant on behalf of yourself, your users, and other parties you represent that you will not:

1. modify, copy, prepare derivative works of, decompile, or reverse engineer any materials and software contained on this website;
2. remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from any materials and software on this website;
3. transfer the materials to another person or “mirror” the materials on any other server;
4. knowingly or negligently use this website or any of its associated services in a way that abuses or disrupts our networks or any other service Lioneur provides;
5. use this website or its associated services to transmit or publish any harassing, indecent, obscene, fraudulent, or unlawful material;
6. use this website or its associated services in violation of any applicable laws or regulations;
7. use this website in conjunction with sending unauthorized advertising or spam;
8. harvest, collect, or gather user data without the user’s consent; or
9. use this website or its associated services in such a way that may infringe the privacy, intellectual property rights, or other rights of third parties.

### Intellectual Property

The intellectual property in the materials contained in this website are owned by or licensed to Lioneur and are protected by applicable copyright and trademark law. We grant our users permission to download one copy of the materials for personal, non-commercial transitory use.

This constitutes the grant of a license, not a transfer of title. This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions or the Terms of Service, and may be terminated by Lioneur at any time.

### User-Generated Content

You retain your intellectual property ownership rights over content you submit to us for publication on our website. We will never claim ownership of your content, but we do require a license from you in order to use it.

When you use our website or its associated services to post, upload, share, or otherwise transmit content covered by intellectual property rights, you grant to us a non-exclusive, royalty-free, transferable, sub-licensable, worldwide license to use, distribute, modify, run, copy, publicly display, translate, or otherwise create derivative works of your content in a manner that is consistent with your privacy preferences and our Privacy Policy.

The license you grant us can be terminated at any time by deleting your content or account. However, to the extent that we (or our partners) have used your content in connection with commercial or sponsored content, the license will continue until the relevant commercial or post has been discontinued by us.

You give us permission to use your username and other identifying information associated with your account in a manner that is consistent with your privacy preferences, and our Privacy Policy.

### Liability

Our website and the materials on our website are provided on an ‘as is’ basis. To the extent permitted by law, Lioneur makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties including, without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property, or other violation of rights.

In no event shall Lioneur or its suppliers be liable for any consequential loss suffered or incurred by you or any third party arising from the use or inability to use this website or the materials on this website, even if Lioneur or an authorized representative has been notified, orally or in writing, of the possibility of such damage.

In the context of this agreement, “consequential loss” includes any consequential loss, indirect loss, real or anticipated loss of profit, loss of benefit, loss of revenue, loss of business, loss of goodwill, loss of opportunity, loss of savings, loss of reputation, loss of use and/or loss or corruption of data, whether under statute, contract, equity, tort (including negligence), indemnity, or otherwise.

Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.

### Accuracy of Materials

The materials appearing on our website are not comprehensive and are for general information purposes only. Lioneur does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on this website, or otherwise relating to such materials or on any resources linked to this website.

### Links

Lioneur has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its website and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement, approval, or control by Lioneur of the site. Use of any such linked site is at your own risk and we strongly advise you make your own investigations with respect to the suitability of those sites.

### Refunds

Lioneur is not responsible for any products or shipping that are bought on the Lioneur Platforms (Web, Android, IOS, Windows). These are **not** products of Lioneur Platforms. It is the product of members on the Lioneur Platform. Therefore there will be no refund from Lioneur.

If you have any concerns or noticed spam or fraud, please contact us immediately at [\[email protected\]](https://lioneur.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) with the subject “Fraud or Spam”. Our personnel will then take action.

Lioneur will not refund membership or advertising costs. Please feel free to contact us if you have any questions and let us help you get the most out of your advertising and membership.

### Advertising

Lioneur has the right to remove advertising or posts made by members. Lioneur can or may block or remove users from all the Lioneur Platforms. Please contact us ([\[email protected\]](https://lioneur.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)) for more questions on what you may advertise and what not to advertise.

### Points earned by users

Lioneur has the right to remove or add points for a member. Points are not “cash” or any form of physical money you can withdraw. It is only allowed on Lioneur Platforms. This is only a point system to encourage users to do more on the Lioneur Platforms.

### Right to Terminate

We may suspend or terminate your right to use our website and terminate these Terms of Service immediately upon written notice to you for any breach of these Terms of Service.

### Severance

Any term of these Terms of Service which is wholly or partially void or unenforceable is severed to the extent that it is void or unenforceable. The validity of the remainder of these Terms of Service is not affected.

### Governing Law

These Terms of Service are governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of South Africa. You irrevocably submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts in that State or location.

\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_

**Lioneur Community Member’s Confidentiality Pledge**
-----------------------------------------------------

All members and staff of the Lioneur community agree to abide by the duties and obligations in the following pledge:

I will abide by the “Confidentiality Standards” below; and

I will abide by the “[Terms and Use](https://lioneur.com/terms/terms)” of Lioneur’s websites and Android & IOS platforms (the “Sites”).

**Confidentiality Standards**

The following confidentiality standards will be observed by all within the Lioneur community.

**Non-Disclosure**

Confidential issues and information shared between members of the Lioneur community are not to be discussed with or revealed to any other person or organization without the prior permission of all parties involved. This includes but is not limited to issues and information shared: in groups, pages, forums meetings, and one-to-ones (online chats); and via any Lioneur Sites, web properties, or Lioneur community networking vehicles.

**Contacting Others**

Issues raised within the Lioneur community are often confidential and are not common knowledge within the community or within members’ companies. When contacting a Lioneur member about such an issue, please use the utmost circumspection. In particular, use care when talking to Lioneur members’ employees, calling or e-mail to members that may be viewed by other parties, and when leaving voicemail messages in general voicemail boxes.

**Usernames and Passwords**

Access to Lioneur Sites and the information contained therein is to be protected at all times and users must take all necessary safeguards to secure their personal username and password information. Do not share your password with anyone else, if you believe your password may have been lost or stolen please contact the Lioneur Support desk ([\[email protected\]](https://lioneur.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)) and we will change it for you.

**Solicitation**

All users of Lioneur Sites agree that the directories and e-mail addresses contained within Lioneur Sites will not be used for solicitation of business by any member of the Lioneur community (including staff). This information may not be used to compile marketing or contact lists of any kind.

**Competition and Hiring**

All members of the Lioneur community agree not to use any non-public information posted on the Sites or shared within the Lioneur community to directly or indirectly, either individually or with others, compete with; solicit customers, employees or business away from;or otherwise cause economic loss to, any other member of the Lioneur community.

**Reminder**

Despite best efforts to ensure confidentiality and security, no site can be guaranteed to be 100% secure 100% of the time. Use caution with all of your Internet transactions.

Although members agree to hold in full confidentiality anything discussed in their group, page, forum meetings, and during one-to-one conversations (online chats), this agreement is not binding on third parties or in a court of law. Members could be compelled to testify on matters discussed in meetings or on Lioneur discussion boards and forums, and Lioneur may be required to disclose information or materials pursuant to applicable laws, regulations, orders, subpoenas or other processes of law. Therefore, members should generally exercise caution when discussing anything in a Lioneur meeting or on a Lioneur discussion board or forum that a member would not want disclosed in any legal proceeding. Furthermore, members of publicly traded companies should seek the advice of their corporate counsel regarding disclosure of any material, non-public information in light of applicable securities laws and regulations.

In addition, because member issue recordings are not ‘privileged’ (i.e., not protected from disclosure under the law), a court could compel Lioneur to release a copy of the issue recording or discussion thereof if a copy of an issue were to be uploaded to a Lioneur web property or if members engaged in a discussion of such an issue in a Lioneur forum or discussion area. Thus, our best practice recommendation is for members to receive their copy of any issue recorded at their meeting because of the possibly sensitive nature of issues.  Similarly, we recommend that discussions of issues containing potentially confidential or sensitive information not take place on Lioneur web properties if the participants wish to keep such discussions privileged.

You acknowledge that Lioneur cannot control, monitor, or be responsible for the conduct of members, Chairs or Speakers or Staff, and that disputes or claims arising out of violations of this Pledge shall remain between the disputing parties without liability to Lioneur.

#### Hosting and Maintenance

Lioneur Hosting Terms and Conditions

Effective Date: September 01, 2017

1. Introduction Lioneur Hosting is a provider of web hosting services. This document outlines the terms and conditions that apply to hosting websites with Lioneur Hosting.
    
2. Migration of Old Websites You agree that Lioneur Hosting will not be liable for any issues that may arise during the migration of an old website to Lioneur Hosting's servers. This includes, but is not limited to, compatibility issues with themes and plugins and the potential for the website to break when using a later PHP version.
    
3. Maintenance and Content Updates You accept the risk that the website may break when requesting maintenance or content updates and Lioneur Hosting will not be liable for any issues that may arise as a result.
    
4. Access to Website You agree that Lioneur Hosting may need to log in to your website to perform updates and Lioneur Hosting will not be liable for any security breaches that may occur as a result.
    
5. Security Lioneur Hosting will not be liable for any hacking attempts or other types of attacks on your website.
    
6. Non-Maintenance of Website Lioneur Hosting will not be liable for any issues that may arise from a website that was developed but never maintained.
    
7. Plugin Costs and Renewal Costs Lioneur Hosting will not be liable for any costs associated with plugins or their renewal.
    
8. Email Lioneur Hosting will not be liable for any email that is not sent from your website.
    
9. Version Maintenance Lioneur Hosting will not be liable for any issues that may arise from not maintaining the versions (WordPress, Laravel, Moodle) of your website.
    
10. Invoicing You agree that if an invoice remains unpaid for more than 15 days, Lioneur Hosting has the right to terminate your hosting services.
    
11. Limitation of Liability Lioneur Hosting provides hosting services only and does not maintain your website. Lioneur Hosting shall not be liable for any damages or losses resulting from the use of its services.

### Email: [\[email protected\]](https://lioneur.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

### Twitter: [@lioneur](https://twitter.com/lioneur)

© 2024 Lioneur. All Rights Reserved.
